boredteachers.com 2018-06-26

# Bored Teachers | Privacy Policy

**The information we collect:**

Bored Teachers may now or in the future ask to collect information such as your full name, e-mail address, date of birth for the purpose of sending you newsletters, filling out surveys, running contests, for promotions or other site-related features. However, this information will be collected through a form completed by you only. Choosing to fill out this form and provide us with this information will confirm your full consent and agreement to providing us with it. You may choose not to provide us with this information and visit our website anonymously. You may also unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.

Furthermore, we do collect other non-personally identifiable information in the purpose of analyzing the traffic and its behavior on our website, managing screen resolution as well as visitor browser type.

We may use your IP address to understand problems related to our server, to analyze the demographics on our website, to understand the popularity of the different sections of our website, and to manage our site.

Bored Teachers uses Google Analytics (Google, Inc. “Google”), which is a web analytics service.

Your personally identifiable information is not disclosed (sold, traded, or transferred) to outside parties, aside from trusted third parties (such as, but not limited to Google analytics – Google, Inc.), who help us analyze, manage our website, or providing services to our users as long as these third parties respect and agree to keep this information private and confidential.

Your personal information may however be revealed when we believe it is suitable to comply with the law, to execute the policies of our site, or to defend our or others safety, properties and rights. (For further reasons such as advertising or marketing, non-personally identifiable users’ information may now or in the future be revealed to relevant third parties)

**Protection of information:**

Our commitment to keep information from unauthorized access, disclosure, destruction or others is real and of good faith, however we do not use special encryption methods, but only use normal security procedures at the moment and therefore cannot ensure total security.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are small files that require authorization from you to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. These cookies assist in analyzing web traffic, as well as your behavior and preferences on the web. You may choose to accept or refuse the use of cookies.

We do use “cookies” in order to analyze our website’s traffic and improve our website in a way that will fit better our users experience and needs. 3rd party websites that our website may link to have their own privacy policy, and, we are in no way related nor responsible for any use of cookies or information collection from those 3rd parties. You may always check 3rd parties privacy policy in order to understand better their procedures.

**Ads on Bored Teachers:**

3rd parties such as online advertisement servers or networks may send advertisement that might be of interest to you to your browser or mobile device. They will then collect your IP address to analyze the dynamic of their own ads and may collect other Non- Personally Identifiable Information.

We are not related nor responsible for these third parties’ privacy policies, and you should check with them for any further information or request.

Many online advertisement companies are part of the NAI, and you may want to check with them to receive more information about these procedures and choose whether you want them to use your information or not. For further information, please ([CLICK HERE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

**Children’s Privacy:**

The use of BoredTeachers.com is not directed at children, especially not at children of less than 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children and request that any under-age person must not send us any. If we did collect children’s information, it will be removed and deleted from our systems as soon as we become aware of it. If you believe or are aware that we have Personally Identifiable Information of a children, please contact us at info@boredteachers.com.

**Privacy Policy Changes:**

This privacy policy is effective from June 1st 2016, but BoredTeachers.com reserves the right to change it at the company’s full discretion, without the user’s explicit consent. We therefore invite you to come check this page as often as possible for any changes and updates concerning our privacy policy.
